Hey, what can I say?
I think you can say, I'm a fascist.
Yeah, I am.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Absolutely.
I'm just checking who's clapping,
just to get my set of where everyone is on this.
Because you know that millions of people
are going to be watching you on YouTube
and checking out who the fascists and the Nazis are.
I'm not ashamed of that whatsoever.
No, clearly you're not.
Clearly you're not.
During the pre-war period, prior to World War II,
it was only those parties that properly
enacted the people's will.
That's why they won.
The conservatives were fat cats.
Are you in favor of killing people who aren't like you?
Quite frankly, I'm not.
You mentioned Franco earlier.
Franco killed a lot of innocent people.
Oh, well, he killed communists.
He killed people who raped nuns and killed priests.
What about children who he killed and women who he killed?
What are you talking about?
He never killed any women or children.
He was Catholic, dude.
He only killed combatants.
Is that what you're claiming?
Yeah, he only killed combatants.
He never killed any innocent people.
The white terror was only punishing those people
who did acts of terrorism.
And again, are you supporting raping innocent women?
Nuns, dude.
Killing priests?
I mean, priests don't brandish guns and kill people.
You just refused to condemn the Nazi Holocaust, my friend.
I don't think you're in a position to ask anyone any questions.
I quite frankly don't care what you think about me.
If I'm a Nazi and being a Nazi...
And the feeling is mutual.
...and being a Nazi means upholding human dignity?
Because I even believe in your dignity.
I don't...
In a state that I was running...
With the greatest respect.
...I wouldn't want to hurt you or anything like that.
But quite frankly...
I don't debate fascists.
Okay.
So do you concede then?
I mean, why...
Do I concede you're a fascist who won't condemn the Nazis?
Yeah.
Yes, I concede that.
Okay, great.
So, I mean, what are we doing here?
Because, I mean...
I don't know what you're doing here, to be honest.
...you just seem offended, to be quite frankly.
I'm offended by people who can't condemn the Nazis.
Yes, I am.
Okay.
Well, I condemn the evils that they did,
but I don't really care about being...
Against the Jews?
Yeah, sure.
I don't care about being called a Nazi, is the whole thing.
I never called you a Nazi.
You called yourself a Nazi, a fascist, and a General Franco supporter.
Well, yeah, I am a General Franco supporter.
He was awesome.
He was super cool, quite frankly.
Because the whole thing...
And you don't believe in democracy?
I don't believe in democracy.
What are you doing here at a televised debate?
This is democracy.
Don't put a debate in disagreement.
Because it is the means to support an end.
The reason we have free speech now is because we want to be openly talking
about our opinions so we can get the state that we want.
But it doesn't mean upholding free speech after we win.
Again, I've mentioned...
The only good thing about this fascist moment we're in...
The whole reason...
...is that you guys are so open about it.
Say the quiet part loud. Keep saying it.
The whole reason I mentioned Carl Schmitt earlier,
and you kind of blew past him, is the friend-enemy distinction.
Blew past him because of the Nazi point.
Even liberals, when they take power,
they want to enact policies,
and they want to enact protections for their people and their ideas.
And they're willing to punish their enemy.
And so I'm the same way.
I'm like, hey, if you're going to punish me,
I'm going to get in power,
and I'm going to frankly punish you when you try to leverage power against me.
Just that simple.